financialchat.com 2003-04-10

# Financial Chat Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Financial Chat, Inc. is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information Financial Chat may gather about individuals who visit its Web sites, how that information is used, and Financial Chat's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to Financial Chat's Web sites and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links.

**Site Usage Information**  
Financial Chat gathers "site usage" information from all visitors to the Financial Chat Web sites. Such data is used in the aggregate, to help determine general usage patterns and fine tune layout in order to ensure that our sites are as useful and enjoyable as possible. This "site usage" and statistical information may be made public information at Financial Chat's discretion. 

Please note that Financial Chat does not control all HTML served in conjunction with its sites. Financial Chat sites may include content from other parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. In particular, some of our partners may use "cookies" in ways that we do not. 

**Individual User Information**  
Individually identifiable information will not be released without that individual's prior consent. Visitors are specifically asked for individually identifiable information when signing up to use certain Financial Chat services, such as the message boards or the live chat membership option. In some instances, users may be asked for personal interest and demographic information in order to create a more customized user experience; however these fields will generally be optional. 

From time to time, Financial Chat and/or its partners may wish to contact individual users regarding community news or to make promotional offers. However, such communications will only be delivered to users who have previously approved them. 

**Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy** (Users under the age of 13)  
In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which Web sites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with Financial Chat policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT:

  * Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age; 
  * Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties;
  * Give children the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information;
  * Entice children with the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

Questions regarding children's privacy should be directed to: 

Financial Chat, Inc.  
207 Main Street Suite 6  
Nashua, NH 03060  

Disclosure  
Financial Chat reserves the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself or its users. Where practical, Financial Chat will attempt to obtain the prior consent of the individual prior to disclosing individually identifiable information. As mentioned above, we reserve the right to share aggregated "site usage" information with third parties.
